(Penny:)Okay, that is the lamest excuse
(Penny:)you could've possibly
come up with.
(Penny:)But I get it.
(Leonard:)You do?
(Penny:)Yeah.
(Penny:)Sometimes I worry
you're gonna wake up
(Penny:)and leave me
for someone more like you.
(Leonard:)I don't even understand
why you're with someone like me.
(Leonard:)Why would I want to be
with someone like me?
(Penny:)You know what I mean.
(Penny:)And, you know, maybe the way
I've been reacting
(Penny:)was me sabotaging this, too.
(sighs)
Well, how about we stop
(Leonard:)being so scared
of losing each other
(Leonard:)and just be together?
(Penny:)That sounds nice.
(Amy:)Good.
(both chuckle)
(Amy:)Because...
(Leonard:)I've loved you
since the moment we met,
(Leonard:)and I will keep loving you
until the end of time.
(Leonard:)Oh.
(Penny:)Oh, my God,
that is the most beautiful thing
(Penny:)anyone's ever said to me.
Yeah?
(Leonard:)That's because you're beautiful,
(Leonard:)and your beauty fills my heart
with love and song.